That's it, look at this rocket, hello, one is Mulana, one is
Uddhav, hey,
what are you doing brother, this is a little
disappointing, hey, no one should lift it like this, look,
we will put it, look, we will bring the things, it will go
up and hit the aeroplane,
this
is P, what, hey brother, this is not the only one,
these people can catch it, you will definitely get the award
[Music] hey,
I am safe, so guys, this
championship was organized on the auspicious occasion of Diwali and the
name of this championship is Bomb Blast
Championship Season Time and
whoever will be the winner of this championship got the prize that he will be
successful in love, we ask our contestants,
tell me why do you want this championship so much,
appeal to them to come because you want it
because sir, I
want to marry this Laila, Uchit, ok, but now
why do you want to marry, tell me sir, I am the
person with the biggest bridge in this world, it is
visible, is Virar a person,
tell me the next Laila because you want it so much,
sir, I am the person with the biggest bridge in this world
and till now more than 50
girls have refused to marry me, that is why
I want to marry Silk Uchit  I am
your shoes and this two, I am
asking you since last hour,
yes, so now you tell me, despite being married,
why do you want to win this Laila,
you should tell me sir, tell me this, I, Review, have a
very sad story, Review, she makes
me do all the household work, she makes me cook,
wash clothes, even sweep and mop,
so I decided
that after winning this championship, I will make her do
all the household work, she will make me cook food,
sweep and mop, even get clothes from her, I am a
very mean person, may
God bless you with your championship shoes and
marry this Laila, best of luck, especially let's
start the first round of this championship, it is
for both crops, so let's see
what he does with the bomb and what all he does
with the bomb, he will keep
watching his horses, it is going to be a lot of fun, let's start
irrigation and fashion, start it,
Papa, I am sure, it is absolutely cursed, nothing is
known about the bomb, it is absolutely safe
and this one is also absolutely safe, nothing has been
removed from Bumpy either, that means both the
access  You have put the gas in the second ram so
let's start this is the
second round of the competition guys and let's see
what is this and what is this it has started come let's see what is this
relationship what do I know what does
all this mean
[Music]
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
that I have reached here so let's
see what does this Ankita have to do with
and what does this have to do with the force stop the
lid let's start
so let's see what does this have to do with the bomb
and what does this have to do with the bomb so that it has reached the
third round
what is with the managing committee and
what is it exactly it means we have
reached the final round let's start the
final let's see what is with this
and what is this if this then we all have to do
what is your ass to
win so that this championship has to be
passed as dear festival hmm
[Music]
MP3
loot loot
that
some some some loot people have expressed
And tell me today let's see
what all has happened to Kendra, what is
happening with her, her house is completely torn apart, let's
see what all has happened to her
[Music],
this is the championship, she is dead, so she is the championship
winner,
so she is the winner of the championship, Mr. Suraj
[Music],
first of all I will marry this boy, or
after that I don't know, thank you,
lots of Diwali wishes and congratulations to all of you, the
next video is definitely going to be liked, shared and commented,
so if you subscribe to the channel,
thank you